How do I explain the benefits or
convince my older relative for example
my father to start TRT because um it was
a friend of mine actually who said my
father would really benefit from TRT but
uh he does not want to start off with
that and he told me well I'll just
overcome low testosterone naturally. So
what to say to that older relative?
Yeah, that's a great question and it's
one I come across quite a bit too,
right? Because a lot of a lot of folks
are resistant to taking medication uh in
general. Uh they feel like maybe they're
giving up or like, hey, you know, my my
hormones are, you know, failing. I'm you
know, I'm less of a you know, less of a
man for this kind of thing. I want to
try to do it myself. How can I get it
back naturally? And uh you know, I mean,
things things decline with age is kind
of the way it goes. I mean, nature has
kind of had its way with us and did what
it needs from us. And um you know, but
uh evolutionary we're still you know,
we're still going to be around for a
while. So you know, we're we're we're
done doing what the what the you know,
what nature wants us to do, but we might
have another 40 years left on this
planet. So make you know, make the best
out of that uh you know, that extra time
you have left. Um you know, everyone
needs your own buyin for this kind of
thing. So trying to sell anyone on
anything can be can be tough. So
everyone everyone will end up with their
own kind of thing that will get them to
do what they want to do. Um, you know,
for some older guys it means they want
to be able to have more energy to do the
things they used to do. Um, to either
spend time with their grandkids or put
it back into their, you know, back into
their business or so they can travel.
Um, but in general, I mean, I think it's
it's one of the one of the big pillars
about just staying healthy as you age,
right? I mean, you don't you want to you
want to stay in good in good health in
general. You want to keep a good amount
of muscle mass. You want to keep your
body fat down. You want to keep your
exercise tolerance up. um and
testosterone and hormone replacement in
general can really um really aid that
and it's it's a big it can be a big
help. So it can be um it can be a tricky
thing. Um I think it makes sense for
everyone to check their levels. Ideally
you would have had some levels checked
earlier on in life too. So now you can
check them and see you know how they how
they've actually declined. But uh yeah I
I think it's a lot of our a lot of our
older relatives could benefit from that
kind of talk without a doubt.
Hey,
hey, hey.